all righty today C challenge the cash
stealth fog hit detection bars and
reinforc
cameras so reinforc
cameras except that we're able to
literally hack the cameras from outside
the building with zero repercussions
whatsoever I guess what I'm trying to
say is that it's not worth anything at
all but aside from that we've got
balancing detection and a lot of fog
which I mean combined with h and
detection bars isn't exactly great but
it should be fine so cyber's going to go
over there find a spot and then
afterwards hack the computer or actually
the signal RoR so now we just check for
the power or the switch which I believe
is over there in the archives a bit hard
to see but it's barely visible from the
camera so we'll go all the way over here
we'll run past we'll run off Sprint and
then afterwards cyber will figure out
when it's safe because it's fog
so I suppose what I'm trying to say is
hopefully I don't run in and encounter a
lot of
gods but what we need to do is wait for
these Gods to all leave because of
course we need to so there's one over
there another over there kind of
important to leave them up Conta the
gods are actually moving especially that
far one which is happening right now and
now we'll move hopefully no one walks in
because otherwise this is going to be
very very awkward we disable it we'll
get out of of there and I believe cyber
has found a screwdriver stop going into
the
tree right
then we'll get a
disguise cyber's just going to stay
there and then we
will there is no guard over there that
is not that is literally not helpful to
me I need a guard
somewhere somewhere I can Le this area
is practically useless actually hey hold
on you stay there look at me
look at me and walk towards
me I think the God's walking towards me
let's go over to the door and wait and I
believe cyber should be up on the tree
by
now I can't even tell at this point nope
cyber's over there all right then we'll
wait for the god to move we'll wait for
him to get off the radio and then we'll
knock him out but you really got to move
faster because I did not lure you at a
convenient spot so we just got to wait I
mean it's just waiting right now get
over there go backwards hopefully you
get off radio
before I mean a key card's worth
it I don't like how long it took for why
cyber I don't like how long it took for
you to
actually put your hands up which I mean
almost went poorly and I'm very happy it
actually went well now cyber really
shooting me from a tree right then we'll
go around over here we'll go upstairs
and then we'll go figure out what's
going on now actually we're going to
leave our scramble outside because we
already have the key card and that's
also so we can actually grab a
screwdriver so we'll do that real quick
we'll go back inside we remember that
we're actually trespassing in there and
now all we got to do is figure out where
the screwdriver is which I mean we found
it earlier but once again it's foggy so
it's not exactly convenient and now
we'll move right
in and hopefully not get caught which I
mean is probably not going to happen but
now once we're done with that we will go
upstairs or downstairs for that matter
and figure out where's where we kind of
need to use Stone close that you know
what it's fine and it's
downstairs but since there's no one here
we'll take this opportunity to actually
lockpick this open because it's going to
be infuriating when that happens we'll
fit right through there just in time and
go
downstairs I mean there's not any to
complain about in that case that is
literally perfect so we go do this we'll
walk past all of the Gods and then we'll
use the screwdriver on the panel over
here cyber stop trying to shoot me just
don't all
right there we go we'll go upstairs now
run past this C it's going to be fine we
will actually shut that door now go
upstairs run past all of that and cut
the
wire now hopefully this goes fine
I'm going to lockpick this because I can
really and then afterwards we're going
to help cyber access this area by
opening up this
door so that cyber can probably and
hopefully get one of the Gods so I
actually have a better time down here
but for for now we're just going to go
downstairs and finally open the last
door lots of accessibility highly doubt
there's actually going to be a god going
downstairs all the way there but if
there is might as well use it why not
and now it's just a waiting game the
gods are going to go reset it at The
Archives and then off those are going to
have to take them out hopefully both in
a basement reload our gun while we can I
mean we're probably not going to use it
and I really hope we don't need to use
it but we might need to use
it now all you need to do is go
downstairs right that guard's going out
seemingly so once you're down
here don't walk upstairs
perfect now you put your hands up get
knocked out and I get a free key card
and hopefully cyber takes care of that
guard because otherwise I would be
having a rot of bad time so let's see
what's going on over
there you pay more attention to don't
walk past
it good now keep your attention on
me and walk all the way out out here and
cyber you go deal with that
guard you were supposed to go deal with
that guard it's not that
complicated walk out here and we're
taking out both Gods it's fine actually
I will not complain about that cyber you
go answer that radio and I will just
walk through here because it's going to
go just fine I mean I could have had
another radio to
answer but I
didn't and that's kind of what's
important which means I got to do it
faster we're not I mean we are out of
take takedowns now but we weren't out of
takedowns earlier so we should be really
careful not to
get not to run out of them right now or
not to get caught so we don't actually
have to take on another guard and fail
it so we'll set up this connection it's
going to hopefully go well and then
we're going to go
upstairs and this part's really
important not get caught because the
guards up there and that luring was
incredibly scuffed but seriously cyber
you really got to go get that now I
presume
that don't complain about it get in here
and
start giving cyber disguise was a bad
idea should have shot both
Gods this was absolutely not worth it
right then we'll take the USB and then
we'll go downstairs and cyber's going to
do their best not to get caught then
will'll go down run past all of those
Gods because it's going to go just
fine and now we'll go inside run past
that guard because we can not actually
close the door because it's a bad idea
but also because that's going to go by
real quick or we'll run past all of this
that go over there we'll go through here
and then we will shut that door actually
then get right out of there because
otherwise it might go pretty poorly so
we run out of here run past all of that
and
cyber right then really shooting me
instead of just getting out of there
interesting choice that's a D cherson in
just under eight minutes cheers everyone
have a great time
[Music]
oh